<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BetterDose</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="please_login_to_continue">Please login to continue</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up_underlined"><u>Sign up</u></string>
    <string name="or_sign_in_with_google">Or sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_email">Sign in with email</string>
    <string name="better_dose">BetterDose</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="log_in_underlined"><u>Log in</u></string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="flashcards_logo">BetterDose logo</string>
    <string name="password_repetition">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="fullName">Full name</string>
    <string name="what_are_you_looking_for">What are you looking for?</string>
    <string name="interactions">Interactions</string>
    <string name="diary">Diary</string>
    <string name="caution">Caution</string>
    <string name="purpose">Purpose</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="invalid_email_or_password">Login failed, invalid email or password</string>
    <string name="basic_information">Basic information</string>
    <string name="member_since">Member since:</string>
    <string name="medicine_prescription">Medicine prescription</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="dosage">Dosage</string>
    <string name="medicine">Medicine</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="hello_comma">Hello,</string>
    <string name="my_medication_for">My medication for</string>

    <string name="text_view_4">The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: "Client", "You" and "Your" refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions. "The Company", "Ourselves", "We", "Our" and "Us", refers to our Company. "Party", "Parties", or "Us", refers to both the Client and ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of Netherlands. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalization and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.</string>
    <string name="text_view_6">We employ the use of cookies. By accessing BetterDose, you agreed to use cookies in agreement with the BetterDose Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="text_view_7">Most interactive websites use cookies to let us retrieve the user’s details for each visit. Cookies are used by our website to enable the functionality of certain areas to make it easier for people visiting our website. Some of our affiliate/advertising partners may also use cookies.</string>
    <string name="text_view_cookies">Cookies</string>
    <string name="text_view_license">License</string>
    <string name="text_view_9">Unless otherwise stated, BetterDose and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on BetterDose. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from BetterDose for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="text_view_10">You must not:</string>
    <string name="text_view_11"> - Republish material from BetterDose</string>
    <string name="text_view_12"> - Sell, rent or sub-license material from BetterDose</string>
    <string name="text_view_13">- Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from BetterDose</string>
    <string name="text_view_14">- Redistribute content from BetterDose</string>
    <string name="text_view_15">This Agreement shall begin on the date hereof. Our Terms and Conditions were created with the help of the Terms And Conditions Generator.</string>
    <string name="text_view_16">Parts of this website offer an opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions and information in certain areas of the website. BetterDose does not filter, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their presence on the website. Comments do not reflect the views and opinions of BetterDose,its agents and/or affiliates. Comments reflect the views and opinions of the person who post their views and opinions. To the extent permitted by applicable laws, BetterDose shall not be liable for the Comments or for any liability, damages or expenses caused and/or suffered as a result of any use of and/or posting of and/or appearance of the Comments on this website.</string>
    <string name="text_view_17">BetterDose reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which can be considered inappropriate, offensive or causes breach of these Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="text_view_18">You warrant and represent that:</string>
    <string name="text_view_19">- You are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;</string>
    <string name="text_view_20">- The Comments do not invade any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark of any third party;</string>
    <string name="text_view_21">- The Comments do not contain any defamatory, libelous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material which is an invasion of privacy</string>
    <string name="text_view_22">- The Comments will not be used to solicit or promote business or custom or present commercial activities or unlawful activity.</string>
    <string name="text_view_23">You hereby grant BetterDose a non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, edit and authorize others to use, reproduce and edit any of your Comments in any and all forms, formats or media.</string>
    <string name="text_hyperlinking">Hyperlinking to our Content</string>
    <string name="text_view_25">The following organizations may link to our Website without prior written approval:</string>
    <string name="text_view_26">- Government agencies;</string>
    <string name="text_view_27">- Search engines;</string>
    <string name="text_view_28">- News organizations;</string>
    <string name="text_view_29">- Online directory distributors may link to our Website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Websites of other listed businesses; and</string>
    <string name="text_view_30">- System wide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.</string>
    <string name="text_view_31">These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products and/or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.</string>
    <string name="text_view_32">We may consider and approve other link requests from the following types of organizations:</string>
    <string name="text_view_33">- commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources;</string>
    <string name="text_view_34">- dot.com community sites;</string>
    <string name="text_view_35">- associations or other groups representing charities;</string>
    <string name="text_view_36">- online directory distributors;</string>
    <string name="text_view_37">- internet portals;</string>
    <string name="text_view_38">- accounting, law and consulting firms; and</string>
    <string name="text_view_39">- educational institutions and trade associations.</string>
    <string name="text_view_40">We will approve link requests from these organizations if we decide that: (a) the link would not make us look unfavorably to ourselves or to our accredited businesses; (b) the organization does not have any negative records with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility of the hyperlink compensates the absence of BetterDose; and (d) the link is in the context of general resource information.</string>
    <string name="text_view_41">These organizations may link to our home page so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.</string>
    <string name="text_view_42">If you are one of the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must inform us by sending an e-mail to BetterDose. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Website, and a list of the URLs on our site to which you would like to link. Wait 2-3 weeks for a response.</string>
    <string name="text_view_43">Approved organizations may hyperlink to our Website as follows:</string>
    <string name="text_view_44">- By use of our corporate name; or</string>
    <string name="text_view_45">- By use of the uniform resource locator being linked to; or</string>
    <string name="text_view_46">"- By use of any other description of our Website being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party’s site. "</string>
    <string name="text_view_47">"No use of BetterDose's logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement. "</string>
    <string name="text_view_iFrames">iFrames</string>
    <string name="text_view_49">"Without prior approval and written permission, you may not create frames around our Webpages that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Website. "</string>
    <string name="text_view_content_liability">Content Liability</string>
    <string name="text_view_51">"We shall not be hold responsible for any content that appears on your Website. You agree to protect and defend us against all claims that is rising on your Website. No link(s) should appear on any Website that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights. "</string>
    <string name="text_view_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="text_view_reservation">Reservation of Rights</string>
    <string name="text_view_53">"We reserve the right to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Website. You approve to immediately remove all links to our Website upon request. We also reserve the right to amen these terms and conditions and it’s linking policy at any time. By continuously linking to our Website, you agree to be bound to and follow these linking terms and conditions. "</string>
    <string name="removal_of_links_from_our_website">Removal of links from our website</string>
    <string name="text_view_55">"If you find any link on our Website that is offensive for any reason, you are free to contact and inform us any moment. We will consider requests to remove links but we are not obligated to or so or to respond to you directly. "</string>
    <string name="text_view_56">"We do not ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we promise to ensure that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date. "</string>
    <string name="tv_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="text_view_58">"To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website. Nothing in this disclaimer will: "</string>
    <string name="text_view_59">- limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury;</string>
    <string name="text_view_60">- limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;</string>
    <string name="text_view_61">- limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or</string>
    <string name="text_view_62">- exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.</string>
    <string name="text_view_63">"The limitations and prohibitions of liability set in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort and for breach of statutory duty. "</string>
    <string name="text_view_64">As long as the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.</string>
    <string name="tv_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="text_view_65">Last updated: August 31, 2021</string>
    <string name="text_view_66">This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.</string>
    <string name="text_view_67">We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy has been created with the help of the Privacy Policy Generator.</string>
    <string name="interpretation_and_definitions">Interpretation and Definitions</string>
    <string name="tv_interpretation">Interpretation</string>
    <string name="text_view_70">The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.</string>
    <string name="tv_definitions">Definitions</string>
    <string name="text_view_72">For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:</string>
    <string name="text_view_73">- <b>Account</b> means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.></string>
    <string name="text_view_74">- <b>Affiliate</b> means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where &quot;control&quot; means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.</string>
    <string name="text_view_75">- <b>Application</b> means the software program provided by the Company downloaded by You on any electronic device, named BetterDose</string>
    <string name="text_view_76">- <b>Company</b> (referred to as either &quot;the Company&quot;, &quot;We&quot;, &quot;Us&quot; or &quot;Our&quot; in this Agreement) refers to BetterDose, Ilica 242.</string>
    <string name="text_view_77">- <b>Country</b> refers to:  Croatia</string>
    <string name="text_view_78">- <b>Device</b> means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.></string>
    <string name="text_view_79">- <b>Personal Data</b> is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.></string>
    <string name="text_view_80">- <b>Service</b> refers to the Application</string>
    <string name="text_view_81">- <b>Service Provider</b> means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.</string>
    <string name="text_view_82">- <b>Usage Data</b> refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).</string>
    <string name="text_view_83">- <b>You</b> means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.</string>
    <string name="tv_collecting_and_using_data">Collecting and Using Your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="tv_types_of_data_collected">Types of Data Collected</string>
    <string name="tv_personal_data">Personal Data</string>
    <string name="text_view_87">While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:</string>
    <string name="text_view_88">- Email address</string>
    <string name="text_view_89">- First name and last name</string>
    <string name="text_view_90">- Usage Data</string>
    <string name="tv_usage_data">Usage Data</string>
    <string name="text_view_92">Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service.</string>
    <string name="text_view_93">Usage Data may include information such as Your Device\'s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.</string>
    <string name="text_view_94">When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.</string>
    <string name="text_view_95">We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device.</string>
    <string name="tv_use_of_your_personal_data">Use of Your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="text_view_97">The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:</string>
    <string name="text_view_98">- <b>To provide and maintain our Service</b>, including to monitor the usage of our Service.</string>
    <string name="text_view_99">- <b>To manage Your Account:</b> to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.</string>
    <string name="text_view_100">- <b>For the performance of a contract:</b> the development, compliance and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the Service.</string>
    <string name="text_view_101">- <b>To contact You:</b> To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application\'s push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.</string>
    <string name="text_view_102">- <b>To provide You</b> with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted not to receive such information.</string>
    <string name="text_view_103">- <b>To manage Your requests:</b> To attend and manage Your requests to Us.</string>
    <string name="text_view_104">- <b>For business transfers:</b> We may use Your information to evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Data held by Us about our Service users is among the assets transferred.</string>
    <string name="text_view_105">- <b>For other purposes:</b> We may use Your information for other purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Service, products, services, marketing and your experience.</string>
    <string name="text_view_106">We may share Your personal information in the following situations:</string>
    <string name="text_view_107">- <b>With Service Providers:</b> We may share Your personal information with Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, to contact You.</string>
    <string name="text_view_108">- <b>For business transfers:</b> We may share or transfer Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of Our business to another company.</string>
    <string name="text_view_109">- <b>With Affiliates:</b> We may share Your information with Our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us.</string>
    <string name="text_view_110">- <b>With business partners:</b> We may share Your information with Our business partners to offer You certain products, services or promotions.</string>
    <string name="text_view_111">- <b>With other users:</b> when You share personal information or otherwise interact in the public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside.</string>
    <string name="text_view_112">- <b>With Your consent:</b> We may disclose Your personal information for any other purpose with Your consent.</string>
    <string name="tv_retention_of_your_personal_data">Retention of Your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="text_view_114">The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.</string>
    <string name="text_view_115">The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.</string>
    <string name="tv_transfer_of_your_personal_data">Transfer of Your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="text_view_117">Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company\'s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of Your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction.</string>
    <string name="text_view_118">Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.</string>
    <string name="text_view_119">The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information.</string>
    <string name="tv_disclosure_of_your_personal_data">Disclosure of Your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="tv_business_transactions">Business Transactions</string>
    <string name="text_view_122">If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, Your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before Your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="tv_law_enforcement">Law enforcement</string>
    <string name="text_view_123">Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).</string>
    <string name="tv_other_legal_requirements">Other legal requirements</string>
    <string name="text_view_125">The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:</string>
    <string name="text_view_126">- Comply with a legal obligation</string>
    <string name="text_view_127">- Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company</string>
    <string name="text_view_128">- Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service</string>
    <string name="text_view_129">- Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public</string>
    <string name="text_view_130">- Protect against legal liability</string>
    <string name="tv_security_of_your_personal_data">Security of Your Personal Data</string>
    <string name="text_view_132">The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.</string>
    <string name="tv_childrens_privacy">Childrens Privacy</string>
    <string name="text_view_134">Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from Our servers.</string>
    <string name="text_view_135">If We need to rely on consent as a legal basis for processing Your information and Your country requires consent from a parent, We may require Your parent\'s consent before We collect and use that information.</string>
    <string name="tv_links_to_other_websites">Links to Other Websites</string>
    <string name="text_view_137">Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party\'s site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.</string>
    <string name="text_view_138">We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.</string>
    <string name="tv_changes_to_this_privacy_policy">Changes to this Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="text_view_140">We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.</string>
    <string name="text_view_141">We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the &#34;Last updated&#34; date at the top of this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="text_view_142">You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</string>
    <string name="tv_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="text_view_144">If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us:</string>
    <string name="text_view_145">- By email: betterdose@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_betterdose">Welcome to BetterDose!</string>
    <string name="these_terms_and_conditions_outline_the_rules_and_regulations_for_the_use_of_betterdose_s_website_located_at_www_betterdose_com">These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of BetterDose\'s Website, located at www.BetterDose.com.</string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_the_terms_and_condition">I Agree To The <u> Terms &amp; Conditions </u></string>

    <string name="visit_our_website"><u>Visit our website</u></string>
</resources>